JULIANA DEANTONIO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Frontend developer with four years of experience working with angular and two years with ionic. Advanced knowledge on CSS, SASS, JS, and atomic design. Proficiency and experience in UI/UX. Implementation of SEO practices. Intermediate English skills.

EDUCATION

TECHNOLOGIST IN MULTIMEDIA PRODUCTION 2017-2019

SFNA

SOFWARE ENGINEERING

2021 - CURRENTLY

Universidad Iberoamericana

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

4 YEARS

HATCHLEAF INC - United States

1 YEAR

Worked as a freelance UI/UX developer, creating prototypes in Adobe XD, and implementing them in angular 10. Interacted with the stakeholders for requirements gathering.

GLÜKY GROUP

FEB 2021 - CURRENTLY

Working as a frontend developer making mobile applications, PWA and websites in ionic, designing and implementing web components in stencil, and database management and configurations in firebase and GCP.

PRAXEDES MIDASOFT MAR 2019 - JAN 2021

Worked as a full stack developer as part of an agile development team (scrum). I designed graphic pieces for the application. I participated on their legacy system migration from pure ASP to a distributed application based on REST services in C# backend and Angular 10 as frontend. Worked also giving maintenance to the old system

SENA - Colombia

SEP 2018 - MAR 2019

Worked as a frontend developer. I participated in a research project that sought to measure the carbon footprint of people and companies. I made the UI for the mobile application and the website, as well as the layout in Xamarin and Angular JS. Also served as a mentor for software factory projects

TECHNOLOGY

ANGULAR 4 YEARS IONIC 2 YEARS CSS **4 YEARS** SASS **3 YEARS** 15 **4 YEARS** TS **4 YEARS BOOTSTRAP 4 YEARS ILLUSTRATOR** 80% **4 YEARS PHOTOSHOP 4 YEARS** XD 2 YEARS C# 2 YEAR **FIREBASE** 1.5 YEARS SOL 2 YEARS GIT

CONTACT

4 YEARS

+57 300 759 26 61 Medellin, Antioquia

julideantonio2002@gmail.com